import questionImage from "../assets/question-bucket-4.svg";
export const questions = {
    bucket_name: "Water conservation",
    image: questionImage,
    questions: [{
        question: "Which of the following types of water is commonly used to flush the toilets in our homes?",
        options: ["Blackwater",	"Greywater",  "Yellow water"],
        answer: "Greywater",
        followup_text: "Greywater refers to used water from showers, bathtubs, bathroom/toilet wash basins. After treatment, it can be used to flush the toilets.",
        source: "https://www.pub.gov.sg/savewater/atwork/alternatesources"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Running a tap for 5 minutes uses up to 40 litres of water.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Running a tap for 5 minutes can use up to 40 litres of water.",
        source: ""
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: A 10-minute shower uses up to 90 litres of water.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Taking a 10-minute shower can use up to 90 litres of water.",
        source: "https://www.pub.gov.sg/Documents/5%20tips%20to%20save%20about%20200l%20of%20water%20a%20day.pdf"
    },
    {
        question: "70% of the Earth is covered by water. How much of it is fresh and easily accessible for us to use?",
        options: ["25%",	"10%",	"5%",	"1%"],
        answer: "1%",
        followup_text: "Only 1% of water on Earth is fresh and easily accessible. This is why we should conserve water!",
        source: "https://earth.org/data_visualization/climate-change-and-freshwater/"
    },
    {
        question: "To save water, you should wash clothes when the washing machine is...",
        options: ["Full", "Half full",	"Leaking"],
        answer: "Full",
        followup_text: "Washing clothes on full load is a good habit we should all adopt at home.",
        source: "https://www.pub.gov.sg/savewater/athome/watersavinghabits"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: It takes around 2,700 litres of water to make a single cotton t-shirt.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "It takes 2,700 litres of water to make a cotton shirt. This amount of water is enough for one person to drink for 900 days.",
        source: "https://sustainablecampus.fsu.edu/blog/clothed-conservation-fashion-water"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a water footprint?",
        options: ["Marks we leave behind when our feet gets wet",	"The volume of water used to manufacture certain products"],
        answer: "The volume of water used to manufacture certain products",
        followup_text: "Water footprint measures the water used in manufacturing, as well as the water contaminated during production.",
        source: "https://www.watercalculator.org/footprint/what-is-a-water-footprint/"
    },
    {
        question: "Beer made from recycled sewage water is available in...",
        options: ["Singapore",	"USA",	"Czech Republic",	"All of the above"],
        answer: "All of the above",
        followup_text: "The recycled beers are known as NEWBrew in Singapore, Epic OneWater Brew in USA California and ERKO in Czech Republic.",
        source: "https://www.up-to-us.veolia.com/en/water/first-beer-made-recycled-water-czech-republic"
    },
    {
        question: "The process of getting fresh water out of seawater is known as...",
        options: ["Deconstruction",	"Desalination",	"Decomposition"	],
        answer: "Desalination",
        followup_text: "By removing salts and minerals in seawater, we can get fresh drinking water. This process is called desalination.",
        source: "https://www.pub.gov.sg/watersupply/fournationaltaps/desalinatedwater"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: It is not safe to drink rainwater.",
        options: ["TRUE",	"FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Rainwater is not safe for drinking because it contains microbes and chemicals.",
        source: "https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a40859859/rainwater-not-safe-to-drink/"
    }]
}






	
		





	